<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Desafio DIO - app com suporte a outros idiomas</string>
    <string name="greeting">Hi, my name is Eduardo Abreu</string>
    <string name="resume">I entered the workforce during the renovation of the Mineirão Stadium while pursuing a degree in Energy Engineering. I participated in the electrical, hydraulic, automation, air conditioning installations, and more, and assisted the team that coordinated the contractors responsible for the installations. Later, I replaced one of the three departmental supervisors. After the completion of the project, I was invited to join the maintenance team at the Arena, where I supervise the maintenance team. In this role, which I continue to perform, I created preventive maintenance programs through spreadsheets, management diagrams, hired third-party companies, and created solutions that maintained the installation to national and international standards. In recent years, I have become interested in software development and have created a Windows application in C++ that controls and manages the maintenance teams\' schedule, organizing them. I have also developed a simple tool that schedules various preventive maintenance tasks according to the periodicity of each discipline to keep each employee\'s workload uniform. Later, I created an Android application in Java to facilitate the reading of energy and water consumption at various concessions and stores in the Arena. As I deepened my studies and became more interested in the area, I took the initiative to develop an Android application in conjunction with a REST API using Spring Boot to integrate the legacy maintenance system (Totvs) with a smartphone application that allows the job executor to describe what was done and indicate the start and end times, respecting the legacy system\'s business rules. Currently, I am implementing more features and creating another microservice to consume this data and generate maintenance team production reports and indicators using Spring/Thymeleaf. I try to follow agile methods and coding best practices as much as possible to deliver a maintainable system and always deliver new features and value. My goal is to enter the software development market, focused on learning and carving out my space.</string>
</resources>